Guide to the Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Archives, ca. 1972-1994 RL.00022
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series
  - Theory/Analysis (Women) Subseries (Box 13)
    - Lesbian Mothers and Other Gay Parents (Box 13)
    - Lesbian Separatism (Box 13)
    - Lesbian Women's Studies (Box 13)
  - Regional and National Women's Issues Subseries
    - African-American Women (Box 13)
    - Abortion (Box 13)
    - Anti-Semitism (Box 13)
    - Women and Adolescence/Menarche (Box 13)
      Lesson I Bleed: Female Rites of Passage in Adrienne Kennedy's Plays. Paper by Rosemary Curb, Eng. Dept, Rollins College
    - Women and the Arts (Box 13)
    - Chemical Dependencies (Box 13)
    - Childbirth (Box 13)
    - Children (Box 14)
    - Consciousness-Raising (women) (Box 14)
    - Contraception (Box 14)
    - Cooperatives (Box 14)
    - Disabled Women (Box 14)
    - Ecology and Women (Box 14)
      (including Anti-Nuke, The Rape of the Land)
    - Education and Women (Box 14)
    - Empowerment (Box 14)
      Women's Empowerment: A Conceptual Framework for Feminist Therapy. Dissertation by Susan Elizabeth Barrett, 1980.
    - Fat and Women (Box 14)
    - The Nuclear Family and Women (Box 14)
    - F.B.I./Grand Jury Abuse (Box 14)
    - Government Studies on Women (Box 14)
    - Health Care (Box 14)
    - Lesbian Health Concerns (Box 14)
    - Women's History (Herstory) (Box 14)
    - Jewish Women (Box 14)
    - Mental Health (Box 14)
    - Mental Health: A Radical Feminist Model of Psychological Disability (Box 14)
    - International Women's Day (Box 14)
    - Women's Pre-History and Mythology (Box 14)
    - Law (includes People's College Law) (Box 14)
    - Women and the Land (women's land trusts) (Box 14)
    - Women and the Military (Box 14)
    - Older Women (Box 14)
    - Women and the Anti-Nuclear Movement (Box 14)
    - Peace Movement, Women and (Box 14)
    - Women in Prison, Women and the Legal System, Women and Police (Box 14)
    - Women in Politics and Law (Box 14)
    - Women and Pornography (Box 14)
    - Rape Task Force (Box 14)
    - Racism (Box 15)
    - Rape and Violence to Women (Box 15)
    - Religion, Women and (Box 15)
    - Rural Women (Box 15)
    - Self-Defense (Box 15)
    - Self-Exam (Box 15)
    - Sexism and Women's Oppression (Box 15)
    - Women and Sexuality (Box 15)
      General
      Folder contains "The Asexual Manifesto" (1972) by Lisa Orlando of the Asexual Caucus of the New York Radical Feminists.
    - (Hetero)Sexuality and Love (Box 15)
    - Spirituality and Women (see also Religion) (Box 15)
    - Sterilization (Box 15)
    - Venereal Disease (Box 15)
    - Women and Sports (Box 15)
    - Women and Studies (Academe) (Box 15)
    - Women's Studies (Box 15)
    - Women and Welfare (Box 15)
    - Women and Work (Box 15)
    - Women and Work: Women's Businesses (Box 15)
    - Women at Work: Sex Discrimination (Box 15)
    - Work: US. Women's Bureau, Labor (Box 15)
    - Work: Pro-ERA (Box 15)
    - Work: Anti-ERA (Box 15)
  - Gay Groups (Atlanta and Southeast Region) Subseries
    - AID Atlanta (Box 15)
    - Atlanta Gay Center/Atlanta Gay Coalition (Box 15)
    - Atlanta Pride Celebrations (LGT - Lesbian/Gay/Transperson) [See also Box 20] (Box 15)
    - Atlanta Men's Center (Box 15)
    - American Civil Liberties Union of Georgia (Box 15)
    - Bet Haverim: A Synagogue for the Lesbian and Gay Community (Box 15)
    - Black and White Men Together (Box 15)
    - Directories of Gay Organizations (Box 15)
    - First Tuesday (Atlanta) (Box 15)
    - Fourth Tuesday (Box 15)
    - Gay Liberation Front - Atlanta (Box 15)
    - Gay Nurse's Union/Alliance (Box 15)
    - Integrity (Box 15)
    - Lesbian/Gay Police Advisory Committee (Box 15)
    - Metropolitan Atlanta Council of Gay and Lesbian Organizations (Box 15)
    - Metropolitan Community Church - Atlanta and Others (Box 15)
    - Presbyterians for Lesbian and Gay Concerns (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Gay Organizations and Events in Atlanta (Box 15)
  - Gay Groups - Southease Regional Subseries (Box 16)
    - South Carolina Gay/Lesbian Pride Movement (Box 16)
    - Southeastern Arts, Media and Education Project (SAME) (Box 16)
    - Southeastern Gay Coalition (later called The Southeast Conference for Lesbians and Gay Men) (Box 16)
    - Southeast Lesbian/Gay Health Conference (Box 16)
    - Misc. Southeast Gay Groups (Box 16)
  - Gay Groups - Regional (except Southeast) and National Subseries
    - National Gay Groups (Box 16)
    - American Library AssociationGay and Lesbian Task Force [see also Box 10, under "Archives and Collections"] (Box 16)
    - Black Gay and Lesbian Leadership Conference, 1991 (Box 16)
    - Directories of Gay Organizations (Box 16)
    - LAMBDA (Box 16)
    - National Conference of Black Gays and Lesbians (Box 16)
    - National Gay Task Force (News about) [press releases - see also Box 11, under "Media"] (Box 16)
    - National Organization for Changing Men (Box 16)
    - March on Washington, 1993 (Box 16)
    - March on Washington, 1987 (Box 16)
    - March on Washington, 1979 [see also Box 21] (Box 16)
    - Queer Nation (Box 16)
  - International Gay Groups Subseries (Box 16)
  - Gay Theory Subseries
    - Gays and Academics/Higher Education (Box 16)
    - AIDS (Box 16)
    - Coming Out and Parents (Box 16)
    - Discrimination Against and Oppression of Gays, Incidents of (Box 16)
    - Discrimination, Gay: Support Statements Against (Box 16)
    - Gay Domestic Violence (Box 16)
    - General Education about Homosexuals (Box 16)
    - Gays and Primary/Secondary Education (Box 16)
    - Effeminists (Box 16)
    - Gays and Health Care (Box 16)
    - Gay Holocaust (Box 16)
    - International Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Gays and Justice/Legal (Box 16)
    - Gays and Legislation, Current Pro and Anti (Box 16)
    - Gay Liberation, Ideology, Relationship to the Left (Box 16)
    - Gay Lifestyle (Box 16)
    - Gays and Mainstream Media (Box 16)
    - Men's Liberation (Box 16)
    - Gays and Mental Health (Box 16)
    - Gays in the Military (Box 16)
    - Gays and the Police (Box 16)
    - Gays in Prison (Box 16)
    - Gays and Political Office (Box 16)
    - Gays and Religion (Morality) (Box 16)
    - Gays and Sports (Box 16)
    - Third World Gay Liberation (Box 16)
    - Transsexuality and Transvestites (Box 16)
  - National Non-Gay/Non-Women Groups, Events, Etc. Subseries
    - New World Communications (Box 16)
- Cultural Artifacts Series
  Consists of non-print materials gathered by ALFA members, including T-shirts, buttons, photos, banners, etc. See oversize materials for posters.
  - T-shirts Subseries (Box 17)
    Atlanta Organizations and Events (including ALFA, wommonwrites, Charis Bookstore, Atlanta Pride marches 1979-1986)
  - T-shirts Subseries (Box 18)
    National Organizations and Events
  - Banners Subseries
    - "Gay and Straight, Black and White, We Won't Be Silenced in Our Fight," Atlanta Women's Union (Box 18)
    - "No Nukes, Stop Rape," Atlanta Women's Union (Box 18)
    - "Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance" (Box 18)
    - "The American Dream" (Box 18)
      [silhouette of black woman and a long quotation from A Historical and Critical Essay for Black Women in the Cities, by Pat Robinson, June 1969]
  - VIDEO: 1987 March on Washington various news coverage (Box 18)
  - DVD: ALFA-10 1972-1982; Public Access/People TV; Original VHS June 1982(?); DVD copy June 2004. (Box 18)
  - Buttons Subseries (Box 19)
  - Photographs Subseries (see also oversize materials)
    - ALFA houses and members (Box 19)
    - ALFA Cat Show (Box 19)
    - women's festivals (Box 19)
    - ALFA Scrapbooks, 2 (Box 19)
  - ARMBAND: pink triangle on lavender cloth (Box 19)
  - BUMPER STICKER: "Sisterhood Feels Good" (Box 19)
  - LABEL: "This Insults Women" (Box 19)
- Margo George Series
  ALFA member Margo George, who maintained an extensive collection of subject files, donated all or part of her personal files to the archives.
  - Africa (Box 20)
  - Aging (Box 20)
  - ALFA (Box 20)
  - ALFA Outreach (Box 20)
  - Battered Women (Box 20)
  - Boogie Women (Box 20)
  - Briggs Initiative (Proposition #6, California) (Box 20)
  - Capital Punishment (Box 20)
  - COGE (Committee on Gay Education) Emory (Box 20)
  - Cuba (Box 20)
  - Cuba Festival Committee 1978 - Atlanta (Box 20)
  - Cuba Festival Committee 1978 - Reprint article in Atalanta (Box 20)
  - DAR II (Dykes for the Second American Revolution) and Early Women's Union [see also Box 22.] (Box 20)
  - Ecology (Box 20)
  - Economics (Box 20)
  - Electoral Politics (Box 20)
  - El Salvador (Box 20)
  - ERA (Box 20)
  - Fat Liberation (Box 20)
  - Fundraising (Box 20)
  - Gay Groups (Box 20)
  - Gay and Lesbian Struggles (Box 20)
  - International Women's Day (Box 20)
  - Iran (Box 20)
  - Cathy Karrass's File [Margo George's lover] (Box 20)
  - Klan (Box 20)
  - Latin America (Box 20)
  - Lavender Anniversary - Gay Pride 1979 (Box 20)
  - Left (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1982 (Lesbian/Gay/Transperson) (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1981 (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1981 - Media (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1981 - Mark McIntire (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1981 - Reorganization Proposal (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1980 (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1980 - Calendars (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1980 - Press Packet (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1980 - Proclamation (Box 20)
  - LGT Pride 1980 - Publicity (Box 20)
  - Lesbian Network (Box 20)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1979 (Local) (Box 21)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights 1979 (Nat'l) (Box 21)
  - Military (Box 21)
  - Military-Industrial (Box 21)
  - New American Movement (NAM) (Box 21)
  - New Right (Box 21)
  - Nuclear (Box 21)
  - Pornography (Box 21)
  - PrisonWomen (Box 21)
  - Publicity (Box 21)
  - Rape (Box 21)
  - Reagan (Box 21)
  - Reproduction (Box 21)
  - ResourcesOrganizing (Box 21)
  - Speaker's Workshop (Box 21)
  - Socialist Feminism (Box 21)
  - South (Box 21)
  - Susan Saxe (Box 21)
  - Third World Groups (Box 21)
  - Underdevelopment (Box 21)
  - Wicca (Box 21)
  - Women's Groups (NOW, etc.) (Box 21)
  - Women - International (Box 21)
  - Women - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Women - Non-Traditional Jobs (Box 21)
  - Women's Union (Atlanta) (Box 21)
  - Women's Union - Action Sheets (Box 21)
  - WRFG Radio Station (Box 21)
- Other Feminist Organizations Series
  The SFLA acquired the archives of other lesbian and feminist groups in the Southeast, six of which are partially represented here.
  - Atlanta Center for Feminist Studies Subseries (Box 22)
    [ 2 ALFA members, Sally Gordon and Elizabeth Knowlton, belonged to the Center. This file contains Gordon's ACFS files from 1984-1986, including minutes and correspondence.]
  - Atlanta Socialist-Feminist Union Subseries
    - 4 volumes:
      - Red cloth notebook w/hand-painted cover, AWU plus ankh symbol: contains flyers for Atlanta Women's Union events (Box 22)
      - Green binder w/minutes of meetings, 1/24/78-7/7/81 (Box 22)
      - Grey speckled accordion file containing Atlanta Journal and Constitution newspaper clippings, 1973-1974, on following subjects:
        - Black Women and Racism (Box 22)
        - Equal Opportunity and the Law (Box 22)
        - ERA (Box 22)
        - Employment of Women (Box 22)
        - Herstory (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
        - Poor Women (Box 22)
        - Reviews (Box 22)
        - Sexism and Children/Marriage and Divorce (Box 22)
        - Sexism and Men (Box 22)
        - Women and Business/Finance (Box 22)
        - Women and Performing Arts (Box 22)
        - Women and Politics (Box 22)
        - Women and Religion (Box 22)
        - Women and Sports (Box 22)
        - Women's Bodies/Health (Box 22)
        - Women and Other Countries (Box 22)
        - Women in Prison (Box 22)
        - Women in Science and Education (Box 22)
        - Women's Movement (Box 22)
      - Brown accordion file w/following
        - Stationery and Envelopes w/ASFU logo (Box 22)
        - Correspondence, Ongoing (Box 22)
        - Correspondence, Filed (Box 22)
        - International Women's Day (Box 22)
        - Old Notes, Info (Box 22)
        - Song Sheets (Box 22)
        - 1-page description of AWU and its purpose (Box 22)
        - The Atlanta Women's Directory, 1st ed., 1979 (Box 22)
      - file containing copies of letter announcing dissolution of ASFU, August 1981 (Box 22)
      - file containing literature, i.e., broadsides announcing events, films for rental; play scripts; various articles on socialism (Box 22)
    - Loose journals and publications (Box 22)
    - Journals (31):
      - ADA For Your Information (Americans for Democratic Action): April 1982:2; June 1982:3 (Box 22)
      - Blazing Star, May 1979, 2 copies (Box 22)
      - Breakthrough: Political Journal of Prairie Fire Organizing Committee V.2 No. 2, Fall 1978 (Box 22)
      - Citizen's Voice: Citizen's Party Newsletter, 1:2, March 1982 (Box 22)
      - Council on Battered Women Newsletter Supplement, Spring 1981 (Box 22)
      - Democratic Left, 10:3, March 1982 (Box 22)
      - Dialogue, 1:9, April 1982[New Orleans] (Box 22)
      - Fair Measure: Newsletter of Southerners for Economic Justice, 6:1, Fall 1983 (Box 22)
      - Fight the Right, No. 1, May 1981, 2 copies (Box 22)
      - The Freedom Socialist: Voice of Revolutionary Feminism 8:1, Fall 1982 (Box 22)
      - Haiti Alert! Friend of Haitian Refugees #2, March 1982 (Box 22)
      - In These Times, 6:12, Feb. 10-16, 1982 (Box 22)
      - Issues in Radical Therapy and Cooperative Power, Winter 1979, #28 (Box 22)
      - NACLA's Latin America and Empire Report, 9:6, September 1975 (Box 22)
      - Liberated Guardian: A National Liberated Publication 2:10, March 1972 (Box 22)
      - Moving On: Monthly Magazine of The New American Movement, Nov. 1977 (Box 22)
      - The People's Crusader 41:13, 20, July 1979, 2 copies (Box 22)
      - The Prison Newsletter: The Committee for Prisoner Assistance, V. 3, Jan-Feb. 1974 (Box 22)
      - The Progressive: 44:12, Dec. 1980; and 45:5, May 1981 (Box 22)
      - Seven Days: 2:7, May 5, 1978; and 2:12, August 1978 (Box 22)
      - The Southern Libertarian Messenger, 7:12, April 1979 (Box 22)
      - Tricontinental: A Publication of the Organization of Solidarity of the Peoples of -Africa, Asia, and Latin America North American Edition, No. 2 (Box 22)
      - Union W.A.G.E.: Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality. No. 43, Nov-Dec 1977? (Box 22)
      - URPE Newsletter of the Union for Radical Political Economics, 11:5, Sept/Oct. 1979 (Box 22)
      - White Lightning no. 27, May 1974 (Box 22)
      - Workers World: 18:25, June 1976 (Box 22)
    - Publications
      (26, arranged alphabetically by publisher)
      - The Christic Institute: Nicaragua: A Look at the Reality 1985 (Box 22)
      - The Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars, Cornell University, May 1970: Twelve Questions on Vietnam (Box 22)
      - Foreign Languages Press, The People's Republic of China: Peking, 1972: New Women in New China (Box 22)
      - Girón: First Great Defeat of Imperialism in America (Box 22)
      - International Socialists publication: The American Working Class in Transition, Kim Moody (Box 22)
      - Merit Publishers, The Marxist Theory of the State, Ernest Mandel, 1969 (Box 22)
      - New American Movement:
        - The Political Perspective, 2 copies (Box 22)
        - Women Organizing: A Socialist-Feminist Bulletin, No. 3 (Box 22)
        - Working Papers on Socialism and Feminism, 3 copies (Box 22)
      - New England Free Press
        - Cuba and Imperialism: The PreRevolutionary Background by Edward Boorstein (Box 22)
        - Cuba's Workers, Worker's Cuba, by Maurice Zeitlin, 1969 (Box 22)
        - Fanshen' Re-Examined in the light of the Cultural Revolution, William Hinton, 1969 (Box 22)
        - Gold Flower's Story, Jack Belden (Box 22)
        - Hospitals in China, Joshua Horn (Box 22)
        - Marx and the Proletariat, Paul Sweezy, 1967 (Box 22)
        - Where is America Going? Ernest Mandel, 1969 (Box 22)
      - Resources for Community Change: Gonna Rise Again! Economic Organizing for Hard Times, 1976, 3 copies (Box 22)
      - School of Labor and Industrial Relations and The Libraries, Michigan State University: Women in American Labor History, 1825-1935: An Annotated Bibliography by Martha Jane Soltow, Carolyn Forché, and Murray Massre (Box 22)
      - Socialist Workers (campaign literature)
        - A Bill of Rights for Working People: Peter Camejo for President, Willie Mae Reid for VP (Box 22)
        - The Fight for Black Equality: Vote Socialist Workers: Peter Camejo for President, Willie Mae Reid for VP (Box 22)
      - URPE: Union for Radical Political Economics: Reading Lists in Radical Political Economics, V. 3, Winter 1977 (Box 22)
  - Dykes for the Second American Revolution (DAR II) Subseries (Box 22)
    Includes Lesbian Feminist Declaration of 1976, 1 volume minutes (11/10/74-2/27/77?), and minutes from two meetings of the Lesbian Community Workshop. Also see Box 20.
  - Orchid Productions / Lucina's Music Subseries (Box 23)
    Local business booked and produced women's music and entertainment in Atlanta area.
    - Margie Adam (Box 23)
    - Advertising Information (Box 23)
    - Linda Allen (Box 23)
    - Alive (Box 23)
    - Amber Moon Productions, Inc. (Box 23)
    - Berkeley Women's Music Collective (Box 23)
    - Birds of a Feather (Box 23)
    - Joan E. Biren (JEB) (Box 23)
    - Black Lesbian Organizations and Issues of Concern (Box 23)
    - The Blatant Image (Box 23)
    - Nancy Brooks (Box 23)
    - Budgets (Box 23)
    - Jodi Cahn (Box 23)
    - Catalogs (Box 23)
    - Charis Brooks and More, Inc. (Box 23)
    - Chocolate Waters (Box 23)
    - Meg Christian (Box 23)
    - Ginni Clemmens (Box 23)
    - Kate Clinton (Box 23)
    - Coffee Houses (Box 23)
    - Tee Corinne (Box 23)
    - Cultural Affairs, Dept. of, City of Atlanta (Box 23)
    - Dancers/Dance Companies (Box 23)
    - Nancy Day (Box 23)
    - The Dinner Party - Judy Chicago (Box 23)
    - Directions/Maps/Hall Layouts (Box 23)
    - Directories (Box 23)
    - Alix Dobkin (Box 23)
    - East Coast Regional Producers Network (Box 23)
    - ECA/ACES (Educational Center for the Arts) (Box 23)
    - Therese Edell (Box 23)
    - The Ends of Means Committee (Box 23)
    - The Fabulous Scallion Sisters (Box 23)
    - Fallen Woman Productions (Box 23)
    - Fallopian Tubes (Box 23)
    - Fan Mail (Box 23)
    - Femme Films, Inc. (Box 23)
    - Fonda Feingold (Box 23)
    - Maxine Feldman (Box 23)
    - Ferron (Box 23)
    - Debbie Fier (Box 23)
    - Film and Video (Serious Business Company) (Box 23)
    - Cathy Fink (Box 23)
    - Flyer LayoutsOriginal Photo Ready Copy (Box 23)
    - Robin Flower (Box 23)
    - Fulton County Arts Council (Box 23)
    - Fundraising (Box 23)
    - Kay Gardner (Box 23)
    - Gayle Marie (Box 23)
    - Mary Gemini (Box 23)
    - Georgia Council for the Arts and Humanities (Box 23)
    - Goethe Institute (Atlanta-German Cultural Center) (Box 23)
    - Hall Rentals (Box 23)
    - Barbara Hammer/Goddess Films (Box 23)
    - Harsuite (Box 23)
    - Hearing Impaired Organizations and Issues of Concern (Box 23)
    - Barbara Higbie (Box 23)
    - Hotel Accommodations (Box 23)
    - Margaret Hults (Box 23)
    - Incorporation (Box 23)
    - Izquierda Ensemble (Box 23)
    - Laurie James (Box 23)
    - Jasmine (Box 23)
    - Jewish Lesbian Organizations and Issues of Concern (Box 23)
    - Layout and Printing Info (Box 23)
    - Lesbian/Gay/Transperson Pride Committee (Atlanta) (Box 23)
    - Lights and Sound (Box 23)
    - Diane Lindsay (Box 23)
    - Lucina's Music - Dissolution of (Box 23)
    - Ruth Mackenzie (Box 23)
    - Karen Mackay (Box 23)
    - Matrix Music (Box 23)
    - Magnolia Productions (Box 23)
    - Mailing List Literature (Box 23)
    - Medusa Music (Box 23)
    - June Millington (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous Performers (Box 23)
    - Mischief (Box 23)
    - Charlie Murphy (Box 23)
    - Sharon Murphy (Box 23)
    - Music Festivals (Box 23)
    - Amina Claudine Myers (Box 23)
    - Naiad Press (Box 23)
    - National Women's Mailing List (Box 23)
    - Holly Near (Box 23)
    - New Woman Press (Box 23)
    - Nexus, Inc. (Box 23)
    - NightRainbow (Box 23)
    - NOW (Box 23)
    - Olivia Records (Box 23)
    - Organizations, Current Newsletters, Etc. (Box 23)
    - Other Voices Theater (Box 23)
    - Michelle Parkerson (Box 23)
    - People's Art Action (Box 23)
    - Janice Perry (aka " Gal") (Box 23)
    - Sue Petersen (Box 23)
    - Pici (Box 23)
    - Production Companies/Notes (Box 23)
    - Publicity/Public Relations (Box 23)
    - Forms - Printed/Xeroxed Extras (Box 23)
    - Judy Reagan (Box 23)
    - Ann Reed (Box 23)
    - Reel World String Band (Box 23)
    - Revenue, Georgia Department of (Box 24)
    - Roadwork, Inc. (Box 24)
    - Beth Scalet (Box 24)
    - Judith Schwarz (Box 24)
    - Suzanne P. Shanbaum (Box 24)
    - Linda Shear (Box 24)
    - Woody Simmons (Box 24)
    - Judy Sloan (Box 24)
    - Jan Smith (Box 24)
    - Phoebe Snow (Box 24)
    - Southern Women in the Performing Arts (Box 24)
    - Special Audiences, Inc. (Box 24)
    - Support Staff (Box 24)
    - Sidney Spinster (Box 24)
    - Stationery Design (Layouts, Etc.) (Box 24)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock (Box 24)
    - Theatrical Performers (Box 24)
    - Tickets (Layouts, Voucher Forms, Order Forms, Etc.) (Box 24)
    - Linda Tillery (Box 24)
    - Adrienne Torf (Box 24)
    - Lily Tomlin (Box 24)
    - TortoiseShell Productions, Inc. (Box 24)
    - Teresa Trull (Box 24)
    - Robin Tyler (Box 24)
    - US Postal Service (Box 24)
    - Views From Ten Percent (Box 24)
    - Nancy Vogl (Box 24)
    - Dede Vogt (Box 24)
    - Mary Watkins (Box 24)
    - Cris Williamson (Box 24)
    - J. Wattles (aka "Jay Goldspinner") (Box 24)
  - WRFG (Radio Free Georgia) files
    - Subject files
      - Arts and women (Box 25)
      - Battered women (Box 25)
      - Books (Box 25)
      - Breasts (Box 25)
      - Childbirth (Box 25)
      - Children (Box 25)
      - Community resources (Box 25)
      - Correspondence (Box 25)
      - Cultural (Box 25)
      - Day care (Box 25)
      - Dessie Woods (Box 25)
      - ERA and equal rights (Box 25)
      - ERA, Georgia (Box 25)
      - Lesbian rights (Box 25)
      - Education and child care (Box 25)
      - Georgia Women's Political Caucus (Box 25)
      - Health (Box 25)
      - Feminist radio networks (Box 25)
      - Families (Box 25)
      - International Women's Day, 3/6/75 (Box 25)
      - Intros (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
      - National Organization for Women (Box 25)
      - Labor (Box 25)
      - Lesbian issues (Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Newsletter) (Box 25)
      - Media (Box 25)
      - Health and women (Box 25)
      - Draft (Box 25)
      - History (Herstory) (Box 25)
      - Native American (Box 25)
      - Political feminism: Women in the military (Box 25)
      - Sports (Box 25)
      - Potential news (Box 25)
      - Prisons (Box 25)
      - Rape (Box 25)
      - Resources (Box 25)
      - Religion and women (Box 25)
      - Prostitution (Box 25)
      - Sex discrimination (Box 25)
      - Women's news services (Box 25)
      - Politics (Box 25)
      - Sports and women (Box 25)
      - Statistics on women (Box 25)
      - Women in other countries (Box 25)
      - Women for Racial and Economic Equality (Box 25)
      - WRFG record and tape library--women's listings (Box 25)
      - WRFG women's programming--press releases, publicity (Box 25)
    - Audio Materials
      - 7" reel-to-reel tapes
        - Spinning the Tale of the Goddess I (2 copies) (Box 26)
        - Smith 1 of 2 (2 missing) (Box 26)
        - Suffragist Harold Sheets (Box 26)
        - Willie Rae Bakestraw/Harold Sheets/KKK, Politics 3 (Box 26)